cute.
かわいい
Come on, Kura-chan, sit there.
さあ、くらちゃん、そこに座ってみて
Wrap the skirt up and
スカートを上に巻いて、
Try putting your foot on the side of your hand.
その まま、 横の手のところに足を乗せてみて
Would you like to dye your pants?
パンツを染めてみ?
It's you who looks to the side.
横を見ずらしちゃお前にして
Can I spread it out?
広げてもいい?
Kura-chan, open it.
くらちゃん、開いて
I'm already soaking wet.
もうマンジュルに濡れてるよ
It's shiny.
テカテカしてる
Shall I just take off my pants?
パンツだけ脱がせよっか
Kura-chan, take your clothes off.
く らちゃん、脱がして
Kura-chan, please sit down.
くらちゃん、こそ座って
Try smelling Chin Chin.
チンチンの匂い嗅いでみて
Come on, Kiccho.
さあ、きっちょ
Smell it.
匂い嗅いで
Does it smell?
匂いする?
The smell of dick.
チンチンの匂い
It's already getting bigger.
もう大きくなってきたね
Get licked.
ぺろぺろしてもらう
To the deepest part.
一番奥まで
painful?
苦しい?
Kura-chan, move.
くらちゃん、動いて
Licking it from below.
下からぺろぺろやって
Chin-chin, it's all slippery now.
チンチン、ぬるぬるになったね
Speak quietly.
しこしこしながらしゃべって
Rub your hands faster.
手、もっと早くしこしこして
Suck it hard, chin chin.
いっぱい吸って、チンチン
It makes a loud sound.
ヘンルー音出すね
Kura-chan, stand up.
くらちゃん、立って
Cute face.
可愛い顔
Get it out of your mouth.
口からいっきり出して
Just let it out.
もういっきり出して
Did you take it all out?
全部出した?
A lot was served.
いっぱい出されちゃったね
In your mouth.
口の中
Let's take a look.
見してみよう
It came out great.
すごい出たね
A lot came out.
いっぱい出た
It was dripping.
垂れちゃったよ
Was it painful?
苦しかった?
It was painful.
苦しかった
But it was cute.
でも可愛かった